(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T21:11:32.209604",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
Didn't have the song you wanted to sing?
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Then let's sing on JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 オンデマンド！
JOYSOUND X1 On-Demand!
曲数No.1！
No. 1 song count!
AIが採点 絶賛！
AI scoring & rave reviews!
KARAOKE 最高！
Karaoke is the best!
曲数No.1 歌いたい曲があるって最高
No. 1 in song count! Having songs you want to sing is the best,
JOYSOUND X1
彗星のごとく現われたスターの原石！
A rough diamond appearing like a comet!
バーチャルアイドルの星街すいせいです！
I'm virtual idol Hoshimachi Suisei!
この度、フリューさんからわたしの“新作”プライズアイテムが登場します！
This time, my new prize items from FuRyu are making their debut!
新作アイテムは全部で4種類！
There are four types of new items in total!
みんな絶対ゲットしてね！
Everyone, make sure to get them!
開演までしばらくお待ちください The concert will be starting soon.
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
2025.2.1 21:30 - ライブグッズ2次販売開始
Secondary live goods sales start Feb 1 at 21:30
まもなく、
Shortly,
皆様お待ちかねの、
everyone's long-awaited
開場時間となりますので、
doors will soon open,
少々お待ちください。
please wait just a moment.
皆さん、こんにちはー！
Hello everyone!
イェーイ！
Yay!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To help you fully enjoy the live to the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of recording, audio, or video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
The venue is strictly non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮下さいますよう、お願い申し上げます。
Please refrain from smoking anywhere in the venue.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
Should you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内でのもし、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Actions that inconvenience others or disrupt the performance, such as diving or throwing items onto the stage, are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください。
Please follow the rules and keep the energy up.
また、良い返事！
And... great response!
また、本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Additionally, cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue during this performance, and audience seats may be captured.
はーい！
Yes!
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes, so please understand this in advance.
はーい！
Yes!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#星街すいせい」です。
Also, the live concert hashtag is "#HoshimachiSuisei".
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください。
Please use the hashtag to share the excitement.
はーい！
Yes!
よろしい！
Very well!
それでは、開演まであと…
Now, until the show begins, only...
もう少しです！
a little longer!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's all get hyped up together!
またね！
See you soon!
Baby, baby, baby, boo...
つまらない デイズ もう 散々ね！
Boring days are already over!
奇跡 願っているだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles,
watch me do...
呪術 秘中 トリック 無しのマジック
magic without any tricks or secrets.
I wanna be free! だって まだ 踏み出し
I wanna be free! Still stepping out,
あ、でも まだ フリーデス
ah, but still, I'm free.
Heyタクシー ちょっと宇宙迄
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit.
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔物のよう
The second hand ticks like a monster rushing the night,
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
and life is magic that melts away in an instant.
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り！
If so, run through it just as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin',
あたしは大変身 メイクアップ！
I'm in the middle of a great makeover!
我儘のままに 煌めきに注意
Be careful with the sparkle of your selfishness,
洒落な街で dancin'
dancing in a stylish city.
左様ならグッバイ 劣等感
Goodbye to your inferiority complex,
何時かは喝采 クラップ オウ デ エンス
someday, applause from the audience.
皆々御詠和あれ！
Everyone, join in singing!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混濁がっても仕様がない
even if it's chaotic, there's no other way.
ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight,
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
今夜に明日などない
there's no tomorrow tonight.
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
So those who dance freely win, right?
dance！ ラララリホ
Dance! La la la li ho,
どんな問題も解は一つ
every problem has only one solution.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛する
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes.
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days are already over!
奇蹟願っているだけの人生
A life where you're just wishing for miracles,
watch me do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any tricks or secrets,
I wanna be free!
だってまだふりだし
Because I'm still at the starting line.
hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit.
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔物のよう
Like a monster's ticking clock hurrying the night away,
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法それならば駆け抜けて想い通り!
Life is magic that melts in an instant, so run through it as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってdrivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin',
あたしは大大変身メイクアップ!
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに煌きに注意注意
Careful not to get carried away by selfishness,
洒落た街でdancin'
Dancing in a stylish city,
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Goodbye to your inferiority complex.
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエンス
Someday, applause from the audience—
皆々御歌唱あれ!
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混濁がくても仕樣が無い
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way.
ガラス シューズ で 踊る tonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight.
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
今夜に明日など無い
There is no tomorrow tonight.
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょ？
So those who dance freely win, right?
dance! ラララリホ
Dance! La la la li ho,
どんな問題も解は一つ
Every problem has only one solution.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛する
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes.
本当のあたしの理想
That is my true ideal.
何だか世界は限界の気がして
The world feels like it's reaching its limit.
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
Just being safe is worrisome.
今すぐ jumpin jumpin out
Jumpin out right now!
chitty chitty bang bang chitty bang bang
唯々諾々に危機感抱く日々に
In days when I feel an urgent crisis,
ぎりぎり爆発気味
My explosive feelings are at their limit.
たった今発散してしまおうか
Should I let it all out right now?
まだまだビイビー弾き
Still firing away skillfully,
巧妙に乱射
Firing wildly all around,
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
One shot is simply not enough.
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
Finally, I found the answer for you.
灰になるまで踊って居ようぜ
Let's keep dancing until we turn to ash.
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days are already over!
奇蹟願っているだけの人生
A life where you're just wishing for miracles,
watch me do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any tricks or secrets,
I wanna be free!
だってまだふりだし
Because I'm still at the starting line.
hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit.
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔物のよう
Like a monster's ticking clock hurrying the night away,
白いカーテンの sway
White curtains sway,
似たような朝のようで
Like a familiar morning,
まるで違う交差する星彩
Intersecting stellar colors, totally different.
新しく目覚める "thinking to myself"
A newly awakening "thinking to myself".
定型文の storyteller mic は渡しちゃ駄目
Passing on the formulaic storyteller mic is no good.
安全圏の observer error
Observer error in the safe zone—
何を信じる？
What do you believe in?
oh oh 眩しくて逸らした初期衝動今追従して
Chasing the dazzling, averted early impulse now.
空の愛の歌ばかりで もう聴き飽きてきたでしょ？
You must be tired of hearing empty love songs.
blackout 流星 knock down 寸前
Blackout, just before a shooting star knock down.
退屈してんじゃない？？
Aren't you bored?
"I'm ready to dawn"
千載一遇の new sense で想像
Imagining with a once-in-a-lifetime new sense,
光速の sympathy で oh oh oh oh oh
With light-speed sympathy, oh oh oh...
直感主義の innocence で創造
Creating with intuition-driven innocence,
奇蹟も世界も自分次第で！
Miracles and the world are up to you!
start to know 革命の狼煙は
Start to know, the signal fire of revolution.
start to go 変化を恐れない覚悟さ
Start to go, the resolve not to fear change.
渇いた大地を駆ける唯一の光
The sole light running across the parched earth.
変わりたい・変えたいの連鎖が剥き出しの魂を焚き付ける
The chain of wanting to change kindles a bared soul.
6000万年に一度きりの surprise でドラマティックなキスにしようぜ
Let's make it a dramatic kiss with a rare surprise.
en count！
En count!
光速超え魅せられ まだ醒めない
Enchanted beyond light speed, still not waking up.
夜空に駆けた遠すぎる欠片
Too-distant fragments that raced across the night sky,
惑星が導くレーダー
The radar guided by planets.
what do you need？
What do you need?
what do you take？
What do you take?
望む場所へと yeah yeah yeah yeah
To the place you desire, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
無謀な夢なら青天井 危ないほどアガる high-tension
If it's a reckless dream, high-tension gets dangerously high.
突き抜ける銀河の果てで
At the far end of the piercing galaxy,
please call me now "revolute-meteor"
夢か現か幻かきちんとその五感で確かめて hit me！
Check it with your five senses—dream or reality—and hit me!
モニター越しの輝きじゃつまらない
Shine through a monitor is boring.
飛び出す想像の遥か上 to heaven
Far above the soaring imagination to heaven.
目を逸さず見ててね 自由への黎明
Keep your eyes on the dawn towards freedom.
ah 踏み出した刹那
Ah, the moment I stepped forward,
色付く new days 絶景 update
Colorful new days, updating the view.
希望も絶望も自分次第で！
Hopes and despairs are up to you!
start to know 革命の火蓋は
Start to know, the opening battle of revolution.
start to go 変化を望む強い情熱だ
Start to go, a strong passion desiring change.
渇いた心に満ちた孤高の光
The solitary light filling a parched heart.
壊しては創るの連続が激動の未来を連れてくる
Destroying and creating brings a turbulent future.
6000万年に一度きりの surprise でドラマティックなキスにしようぜ
Let's make it a dramatic kiss with a rare surprise.
"I'm ready to dawn"
...
産まれ落ちた星をただ眺めていた
Staring only at the stars that fell and crumbled away,
君が座っている巨石は醜いか
is the boulder you're sitting on ugly?
僕はここで、その石を壊さないように強く抱いている
I am here, holding it tight so I don't destroy that stone.
二人の足元には同じ影
The same shadow at our feet...
つんのめったり転んじゃったり
With nowhere to go and stumbling around,
無茶もしてきたね
we've done some reckless things, haven't we?
手を伸ばしても届かない事ばかりだったけど
Even when reaching out was mostly out of reach,
悪くないさ何光年だって進もう
how many light-years away is it? Let's keep moving forward!
太陽が今日も昇っていく
The sun is rising again today.
笑ってよ
Smile,
たとえ空がどんなに悲しんでいても
even if the sky looks ever so sad.
何度だって“僕”を歌うからさ
That's why I sing "myself" over and over!
全力で生きていくんだ
I'll live life to the fullest!
いつまでも手を離さないで
Never let go of my hand, forever and ever.
大人の風で初めて惹かれ合うんだね
For the first time in our lives, wrapped in the sunset wind,
大人の風で初めて響き合うんだね
we resonate deep within our hearts!
並んだその表情に
Standing side-by-side with matched postures,
臆病になっていた
I had grown so cowardly.
街の上へ
Upon this town...
叶わない暴力と抗えない重力に
An impossible violence and an inescapable gravitational pull...
何度も何度も引き裂かれている
Countless prayers have been shattered,
なんてどこかで吐き気が
yet somewhere, our paths split apart.
声を奪ったままの君みたいになってたんだ今さら
It feels like I lost my voice and became a completely different person.
戻れない分かってよ
I can't turn back now, so understand!
信じて嘘つき
Believing and lying...
厭になるくらいの想いが渦巻く
It's enough to make me want to cry, my heart is overflowing!
今日も振り回されていく摩天楼足が
Even today, we are swept around in this worldly hustle!
飛び上がる準備をしてる
I'm getting ready to leap off!
何もかも半端で崩壊して滲んでいく
Everything falls apart in pieces, crumbling away.
皆のお手々を返してください
Everyone, please give us a round of applause!
嫌いじゃない好きじゃない
It's not that I hate it, it's not that I like it either.
全部が一つが
It's all... just one thing.
「変わりたい」「解りたい」「どうしたい」「どうしよ」
"I want to change," "I want to understand," "What should I do?"
「聞かせない」「聞かせて」
"Don't let me hear it," "Let me hear it!"
伝えたい
I want to convey it!
愛してる大嫌い大好き
I love you so much, I hate you so much, I adore you so much.
重いくらいの想いが溢れる
It's so heavy, my feelings are overflowing,
今日もまた大好きなんだこの感情が
and today, I'm once again deeply adoring this feeling!
大人の中で初めて惹かれ合うまで
For the first time in our lives, wrapped in the sunset wind,
あなたのその胸で響き鳴すまで
resonating deep within your chest until the very end!
「愛してる」「大嫌い」「嘘だよ」
"I love you," "I hate you," "You're lying!"
「大好き」
"I love you!"
ということで、皆さんこんにちは！
And with that being said, everyone, hello!
では、いつものご挨拶をさせていただきます。
Now then, let's move on to our usual greeting.
水星の如く現れたスターの
Rising from the water like a shooting star,
星街すいせいです！
Hoshimachi Suisei of Hoshimachi Planet!
いいですね 武道館！
Good to see you, Budokan!
水飲みます。失礼します。
Water, please. Excuse me.
まあね、え、しょっぱなからクライマックスみたいな感じになってるんですけれどもしゃ、
Well, it's pretty much all climax right from the start, but...
武道館ライブ「Supernova」いよいよ始まりました！
Hoshimachi Suisei Nippon Budokan Live "Supernova" has finally begun!
うわー、すごい！ついにこの日がやってきたんだが、ね！感慨深いよね、みんな。
Wow, it's finally here. Everyone, it's so moving, right?
はい、え、もうみんな知ってると思うんですけど、え、デビュー当初からね、ずっと、あの、武道館で、ライブをするぞというのを目標にしてやってきたんですけども、
Well, as you all probably know, my goal since debut has been to hold a live concert at Budokan, and I've been working toward it...
ついにね、叶えたということで、あの、本日はサードアルバムの曲をいっぱいやる予定ですので、みんな聴いてきたかな？サードアルバムちゃんと。
and I've finally achieved it! Today, we're going to play lots of songs from my 3rd album. Everyone, have you listened to it properly?
えー！そりゃそうだよね。あ、みんなサードアルバムの中でどれが楽しみ？
Of course you have! Everyone, which song from the 3rd album is your favorite?
わかんない。
I have no idea.
はい、え、今回もツアーと同じくバンドさんを引き連れております。
Right, this time too, we are joined by the same band!
さらに、え、皆さん気付かれたでしょうか？
And everyone, have you noticed?
お、そう、今回はブラス隊もいるんです！
Yes, this time we have a brass section too!
いや、はい、今日しか聴けないようなね、ライブアレンジをバンドさんと一緒にいっぱい作って決めたので、
Yeah, we worked together with the band to create some incredible live arrangements you've never heard before, so I hope you're all looking forward to it.
お、あ、ハードル上げちゃった。
Oh, the bar is set high!
いや、本当にね、いい感じにアレンジされてるので、全部楽しみにしていてください。
Seriously, the arrangements are amazing, so please look forward to all of them!
えー、では、これが押しカメラです。
Well then, this is the "Push Camera."
イェーイ！やったー！
Yay!
え、みんなさ、気づいた？あの、ツアー下はツアーと一緒で、あの、上だけちょっとアタッチメント変わってみたいな衣装なんですよ、今回は。
Everyone, did you notice that for this tour, only the top part of the outfit is different from the previous tour?
わかる！さすがにねって。
Well, obviously!
え、そうなんだよね。そうなんです。あの、ツアーで、ツアーでもう実を切れる、切れたんですけど、この服、もう出来上がってたから。でもちょっと出し惜しみしとこうかな、武道館にとと思って出し惜しみしときました。
Right, it's true! We actually could have finished this outfit for the tour since it was already ready, but I thought it would be a nice surprise for the Budokan, so I saved it.
イェーイ！
Yay!
たくさんスクショしてください！わーい！
Take lots of screenshots! Yay!
可愛い。ピース。
Peace!
なんかこれピースみたいな格好じゃないような。
Wait, isn't this pose a bit un-peace-like?
おー、かっこいい。
Ooh, cool.
はい、え、ライブの感想はハッシュタグをかけめぐる星街でたくさんツイートしてください！
Alright, please tweet lots of your live impressions using the hashtags!
スクショOK。
Screenshot OK!
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方々は、ここまでです！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where it ends!
はい、YouTube、TikTokの皆さんの分まで得いただきました。
Alright, we've made it through to the YouTube and TikTok peak!
え、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい！みんなは概要欄から配信サイトへ飛んでくださいね。こっちか？こっちか？こっちか？
We still want to get hyped up together! Everyone, please head over to the streaming site via the links in the description. Over here? Over there? Over here?
はあー。
Whew.
ということでね、あの、もう、さっきも言ったんですけど、冒頭からね、クライマックスみたいなあの、セトリをしているんですが、私がこのセトリ考えて、あの、バンドリはなったときに、これ、ずっとクライマックスだなって。
Right, as I mentioned earlier, we're maintaining this climax from the very beginning. When I thought about this setlist and we got busy with the band, I kept thinking, "Wait, is it a climax the whole time?"
いや、本当にずっとクライマックスなんですよ。だからもうね、皆さんも感情がもうこんな、こんな、こんな、こんな状態にこうなっちゃうから、あの、ね、あの、水分補給しつつ楽しんでいただければなと思います。
And it really is a climax the whole time, so everyone's emotions are going to get super high like this, so please make sure to stay hydrated while enjoying it!
はあ、あ、今のうちに皆さんあのペンライトみたい。
Oh, and make sure to get your penlights ready soon!
あ、なんか、うちわとか見たい。うちわ。
Oh, I want to see yourうちわ (fans) too! I want to see your うちわ!
おー、おー、ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう！
Oh! Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you!
お、見える、見える、見える見える！うれし！キャラのダメにみんな作ってくれたもんね、いつも。
Oh, I see them, I see them, I see them! They're so happy! You all made them for me, even though it's hard for characters.
みんながいつもさ、ちゃんときれてないからさ、ちゃんときたこと思って。
I always want to see them since I couldn't always see them properly before!
今のうちに。
Now, while we still have time...
この後何が起こるかわかんないからね。よし。
Who knows what will happen next? Let's go!
ちょっと、なんか変なこと言ってるな。別、別に普通のライブが行われますんで。
Haha, I'm saying some weird things. Anyway, the live will proceed normally!
では、皆さん、もう次の曲聴きたいですか？
So, everyone, do you want to hear the next song?
ちょっと乾燥してるんでもう一回お水飲みます。
My throat's a bit dry, so I'll have some water again.
それでは次の曲は
Well then, for the next song,
私の想いを込めて初の作詞に挑戦した
putting my feelings into it, I took on my first lyric-writing challenge—
あの曲です。聞いてください。
it's that song. Please listen to it.
綺麗ごと。
Kireigoto.
綺麗ごとを吐くその口が
That mouth that utters platitudes
君のことを苦しめるから
torments you, so
同じことばかりの日々に ああ意味を求めて寄り添い合うの
in days of endless repetition, ah, we seek meaning and snuggle close.
ひしめき合うカラーフィルターの奥で笑ってる
Smiling behind the crowded color filters,
散々恨んだ狡猾さが
that cunningness I resented so much
今、自分なりの生き方なのに
is now my own way of living, yet
潔癖な思想に縛られたままで
I remain bound by squeamish ideals.
強がるくせに唇を噛む
Even though I act tough, I bite my lip,
分かってない素振りをしてばかり
always pretending I don't understand.
綺麗ごとを吐くその口が嫌いだから歌を歌うんだ
I sing songs because I hate that mouth that utters platitudes,
諦めてるその顔が僕のことを曇らせるから
because that resigned face clouds my own heart.
こんな声だって伝わらなくて
Even though this voice fails to reach,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
and I want to weave more perfect words,
ずっと欲張って
always being greedy,
きっと間違えて
surely making mistakes,
今日も転げ落ちる
today too I tumble down
不完全な朝
into an imperfect morning.
本音も言えない日常にはただ「理想なんて」と嘲笑う声
In a daily life where I can't speak my true feelings, a voice sneers, 'Ideals, huh?'
言い返す言葉も選べずにただ増えていく痛み
Without even choosing words to retort, the pain just keeps increasing.
虚勢を張る衝動で隠して綺麗なままで生きていたいのか
Do I want to hide it with the urge to put up a front and stay pristine?
諦めを塗り重ねて「本当」が見えなくなってしまうんだ
Painting over resignation until the 'truth' becomes invisible.
綺麗ごとを吐くその口が
That mouth that utters platitudes,
that mouth that utters platitudes...
綺麗ごとを吐くその口が嫌いだから歌を歌うんだ
I sing songs because I hate that mouth that utters platitudes,
諦めてるその顔が君のことを苦しめるから
because that resigned face torments you.
こんな声だって伝わらなくて
Even though this voice fails to reach,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
and I want to weave more perfect words,
ずっと欲張って
always being greedy,
きっと間違えて
surely making mistakes,
それでも歌おう
even so, let's sing,
不完全だから
because we are imperfect.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion has ended. Thank you for watching!
Thank you for coming! Please share your thoughts on social media!